Okay, the eyes are basically done.
This is our perfect eye look for Goth.
We're going to do a little bit in the brows.
Her brows are pretty light.
They're nicely shaped, but they're pretty light.
We want them to match more of her dark chestnut hair color.
I'm using a powder and a brush.
You can use a pencil.
It's all personal preference.
I'm just going to fill in her natural brow line.
We don't want the eye brows to look too over done or too powdered, so I'm just going to fill in a little bit just to get a nice natural arch.
The eyebrows really shape the face, especially when you have such a dramatic eye shadow look.
You really want to make sure that you don't forget your eyebrows.
Because her eyebrows are a little short, I'm going to draw just a tiny bit onto the ends just to extend them a little bit.
Add a little more if you want to.
It's all personal preference.
Again, how dark you want your brows to be.
Try to use a color that most closely matches your natural hair color.
Once you get your desired shape, take a little brow comb or brow brush and brush through the brows.
Even everything out.
Blend everything.
What this does is it takes away the excess powder, blends everything in, and also you shape your brow at that point to your desired shape.
Look how perfect that brow looks.